

PRASETIA ADIPRAKASA

Email: pras.adi.prakasa@gmail.com

Phone: +62 81223345493

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/prasetiaadiprakasa

Website: portfolio-prasetiaadi.vercel.app

SUMMARY

My name is Prasetia Adiprakasa and I am an experienced project management with over 4+ years of success in overseeing project teams and delivering projects on time and within budget. cooperate with 5 cross-functional (Engineer, Technician, Operation, Purchasing, HSE and Marketing) team and managing large-scale projects with successful outcomes. Ensure projects are delivered to the standards, while maintaining an effective and engaged team. I am driven to lead projects to successful 100% completion, while keeping a focus on customer satisfaction and makesure the Service-level agreement is above 95% and business goals.

SKILLS

- Collaboration
- Leadership
- Team work
- Communication
- Negotiation
- Problem Solving
- Resource Management
- Software Development life cycle
- Project life cycle
- Risk Management
- Agile/Waterfall
- Administration

- Poject Management tool/Trello
- Ms.Office project
- Valuation
- Document Control
- Budgeting

EDUCATION -

Universitas Kristen Maranatha, Bandung

Bachelor of Management

Universitas Widyatama, Bandung

Master of Management

March 2011- October 2017

September 2018 - October 2020

CERTIFICATION

Fullstack Web Development: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React js, Laravel, Golang, MySQL

The complete guide to React js: Hooks, Redux, GraphQL, Tailwind

EXPERIENCE -

PT Len Railwail Systems - Bandung, Indonesia Lead Administration Project

August 2016 - January 2017

- Manage 5 personnel in the team
- Reporting progress project every 1 week
- Control project finances and reduce costs by 15% every month.

PT Len Rekaprima Semesta - Bandung, Indonesia

January 2017 - April 2021

Project Management Office

- Create a project schedule from 0% to 100%.
- Managing multiple project's
- Collaborate with engineering team to ensure the required materials are 100% suitable.
- Identify risks to minimize the possibility of risks (at least 75%).
- Manage project budgets and increase project profitability by reducing unnecessary costs by 12%.
- Identify and resolve issues in the project that will affect project progress.
- Ensuring each service-level agreement project is above 95%.
- Collaborate with the HSE team to ensure personnel safety while working to achieve 0% accidents.
- Make project dashboard analysis every 1 week.

- Discussion with 4 departements (engineering, marketing, operations and finance) to evaluate for each completed project every 1 year.
- Building and maintaining good relationships with clients and stakeholders.

Honda Autobest - Bandung, Indonesia

October 2021 - November 2022

- Marketing
- Monitor sales according to the target by selling at least 50 units per month.
- Implement strategic marketing programs for sellers.

PT PINDAD GLOBAL SOURCES AND TRADING - Bandung, Indonesia **PROJECT CONTROL**

Mei 2023 - Until Present

- Prepare the project schedule, and provide labor, also include work equipment, and get involved in determining the project budget range.
- Contribute and took control in Pembangunan Sistem Persinyalan dan Telekomunikasi Stasiun Mandai project.
- Provides information on the status of the project on a daily basis.
- analyze the build of quantity for the project being targeted
- Follow up the arrival of materials for the project
- Building and maintaining good relationships with clients and vendor.

INTERES

- Managing Project.
- Project Management
- Frontend Development.